{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","address":"6333 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221","owner":"Tayven Food Corp.","licenseNumber":"078831","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"6/22/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E61000001CD9DDB524C954C0F8459AC90E394540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43968","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","inspectionDate":"2018-10-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"4","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43968","inspectionDate":"10/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"43968","inspectionDate":"10/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"43968","inspectionDate":"10/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Baking and cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"inspectionid":"43968","inspectionDate":"10/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"43968","inspectionDate":"10/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"40066","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","inspectionDate":"2017-09-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40066","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"4-301.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT for cooling and heating FOOD, and holding cold and hot FOOD, shall be sufficient in number and capacity to provide FOOD temperatures as required. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"cold holding","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"40066","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"40066","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"40066","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."}]},{"inspectionid":"39959","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","inspectionDate":"2017-08-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36234","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","inspectionDate":"2016-08-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"2","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36234","inspectionDate":"8/24/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (FRONT AREA)","subLocation":"At the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"36234","inspectionDate":"8/24/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (FRONT AREA)","subLocation":"At the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"},{"inspectionid":"36234","inspectionDate":"8/24/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Chemical storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1798"}}